APARAJEETA DIWYA



(647) 573-9720



apdshah2000@gmail.com



40 Calumet Crescent, Scarborough, ON M1H 1W5

About Me

Hard-working and dedicated salesperson with 1.5 years experience who has positive outlook, friendly personality, and great communication skills. Quick learner and can articulate product specifications clearly, familiar with POS, observes excellent customer service practices and has the ability to assist in marketing and advertising services.

Experience

McDonalds Restaurant, March 2021 - Current

Crew Member

- Cashier/Cash handling for front and drive thru
- Delivered prompt and exceptional customer service by engaging the guest and prioritizing the guest's needs
- Assisted in the upkeep of the company's standards by collaborating with other team members

Adidas Nepal, Durbarmarg Outlet, April 2019 - February 2020

Jr. Sales Associate

- Greeting customers, responding to questions, improving engagement with merchandise and providing outstanding customer service.
- Achieving established goals.
- Directing customers to merchandise within the store.
- Increasing in store sales.

Education

May 2022 - Current Seneca College, Canada

Honors Bachelor of Technology

Computer Science

April 2019

St. Mary's High School, Nepal

High School Diploma

Certifications

- Tesol/ESL Certification
- Graphic Design Certification Udemy
- Python/Mernstack Certification Udemy
- C/C++ Certification Udemy

Skills

- Communication
- Strategic thinking
- Customer Service
- Computer Skills
- Team Player